Murder Victims Families for Reconciliation; Records apap313
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Subject Files, 1981-2007, Undated; 5; 4.2 cubic ft.
  - "The Table of Voices on Alcatraz Island" - Community Conversations (November 23rd and December 14th), 1996 (Vhs 17)
  - Tario Khamisa Foundation, 2000 (Box 4 (5-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - The Tariq Khamisa Foundation - "Violence Forum and Garden of Life", Undated (Vhs 18)
  - Testimony of Jude Aller before the Texas House of Representatives, 1991 (Box 4 (5-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Texas-Victims' Rights Legislation, 2001-2002; Undated (Box 4 (5-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Thoughts on New Hampshire, 2000 (Floppy-disk 37)
  - "Time Out: Perspectives on New Jersey's Death Penalty", Undated (Vhs 19)
  - Today Show - Yates (March 18th), 2002 March 18 (Vhs 20)
  - UMOJA Men's Chorus - Wilmington College at Warren's Correctional Institution, 1997 (Cd 2)
  - "Undeniable Resurrection" - Dedicated to James Byrd Jr. - by Ross Byrd, 2003 (Cd 3)
  - Unidentified Murder Victims' Families for Reconciliation Member Photos, Undated (Box 4 (5-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - United States Senate Bill 1088 - Streamlined Procedures Act, 2005; Undated (Box 4 (5-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - University of Richmond Student Interns, 1996; Undated (Box 4 (5-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Untitled, Undated (Floppy-disk 38)
  - Untitled, Undated (Floppy-disk 39)
  - "Uzbekistan: Unfair trials and secret executions", 2003 (Box 4 (5-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Victims Compensation and Assistance Statue, Undated (Box 4 (5-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Victim Rights in Georgia, Undated (Box 4 (5-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - "Victims Speak Out: Help, Hope, and Healing", Undated (Vhs 21)
  - VIF - "Too Many Victims", Undated (Vhs 22)
  - Virginia Coalition on Jails and Prisons, 1992-1993; 1995; Undated (Box 4 (5-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Virginia Coalition on Jails and Prisons, 1995 (Oversized 1, Folder 22)
  - Washington Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty Newsletter, 2005 (Box 4 (5-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Welch, Bud, 1999; 2001; Undated (Box 4 (5-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - "Who is my neighbor?", Undated (Box 4 (5-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Willet, Jim, 2000-2001; 2003; Undated (Box 4 (5-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Williams, Terry, 1999; Undated (Box 4 (5-Subject Files), Folder 18)